Full stack developer with experience in all stages of the development cycle for web projects. Practical knowledge of numerous modern technologies. Focused on front-end lately yet can work perfectly with back-end. Visualizes the whole thing from the user's perspective to come up with ideas

Work History

and solutions for possible problems.

2020-10 -2022-09

Software Developer

Adven.Tech, Cornélio Procópio

- Worked developing web apps such as a stock management, event, e-commerce and other systems on client demand.
- Helped migrating legacy systems to modern technologies.
- Wrote clean and scalable code for both the back and front end.
- Worked with popular technologies such as Angular,
 React, .NET, C#, SQL and others.

2018-12 -2020-10

Designer

ADRA Brasil, Brasilia

- Designed art for fundraising campaigns.
- Automated daily tasks with VBA and SQL.
- Developed a system with Laravel and Vue to help with hot meals distribution for Venezuelan refugees.

2017-05 -2018-07

Game Developer

Roundstars, Brasília

- Worked on developing single-player and multiplayer games.
- Coded core mechanism, search algorithms and bots Als.
- Designed interfaces and arts for games.
- Wrote clean C# code for games on Unity Engine.

Postgraduate Degree: Mobile App Development

Education

2021-11 -

2022-06

2016-01 -	Degree: Game Development
2018-06	IESB - Brasília, Brazil
2021-11 - 2022-06	Postgraduate Degree: Prog. Analysis And Dev. Descomplica - Brazil

Descomplica - Brazil

ARTUR JUNIOR

Full Stack Developer

Contact

Address

Brasília, Brazil

Phone

+55 61 99836-2112

E-mail

arturcmjr@gmail.com

Portfolio

https://arju.dev

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/arturcmjr

GitHub

github.com/arturcmjr

Technologies Highlight

- .NET
- TypeScript
- Angular
- C#
- React
- SQL
- Git

Essential Skills

- Fast learner
- Self-starter
- Creative
- Critical thinking